<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Turna</string>
    <string name="turna">Turna</string>
    <string name="clean_button">Clean button</string>
    <string name="refresh_button">Refresh button</string>
    <string name="action_button">Action button</string>
    <string name="choose_mode">Choose mode</string>
    <string name="sunny_side_up_name">SUNNY-SIDE UP</string>
    <string name="easy_name">OVER EASY</string>
    <string name="medium_name">OVER MEDIUM</string>
    <string name="well_name">OVER WELL</string>
    <string name="hard_name">HARD SCRAMBLED</string>
    <string name="hard_desc">Scrambled technically means that the whites and yolks are broken and mixed together.\nUse a medium-high heat. In a non-stick pan, heat butter until bubbly, but not brown. Crack your eggs into the pan (or into a bowl if you’re fancy), season, and stir with a rubber spatula. Using a whisk will create a denser texture, if you’re into that sort of thing. Keep your eggs moving. Every few minutes, stir and fold your eggs to break up any large curds, and scrape the bottom of your pan often to stop sheets from forming. Cook until you no longer have visible liquid in the pan, about five to seven minutes. Remove immediately – leaving eggs in a hot pan can leave them rubbery.</string>
    <string name="medium_desc">The egg is flipped and the yolk is only slightly runny.\nHeat a small nonstick skillet over medium–low (closer to low than medium) heat. Add butter. When the butter starts to melt and bubble, swirl it around the pan. Add eggs, being careful not to break the yolks. Season with salt and pepper. Cook for 2–3 minutes or until the whites of the eggs are mostly firm. The yolk will still be runny at this point. Use a thin spatula to carefully flip the egg and cook for 90 seconds more, or until the yolk has desired firmness. If you jiggle the pan and the yolk doesn’t move much, it’s probably done.</string>
    <string name="easy_desc">The egg is flipped and the yolk is still runny.\nThe most common way to make over–easy eggs is fried in a nonstick pan or skillet on the stove. Simply heat a greased pan (you can use vegetable oil or even butter) and crack raw eggs onto its surface. Cook until just set, gently flip, and cook for 20–30 seconds more.</string>
    <string name="well_desc">The egg is flipped and the yolk is cooked hard.\nGrab a nonstick skillet and melt butter over medium–low (closer to low than medium) heat. When it starts to melt and bubble, swirl it around the pan. dd the eggs, one at a time, being careful not to break the yolks. If you’re not comfortable with this, break them in a bowl first. It makes it easier to fish out any stray pieces of eggshell, too! Season with salt and pepper. Cook for 2–3 minutes or until the whites of the eggs are mostly firm. The yolk will still be runny at this point. If desired, break the yolk by poking it with a spatula. This causes it to spread out and cook even faster. Use a thin spatula to flip the egg and cook for 2–3 minutes more or until the yolk is firm and fully cooked.</string>
    <string name="sunny_side_up_desc">The egg is fried with the yolk up and is not flipped.\nHeat oil in an 8-inch nonstick skillet over medium-low. Gently crack eggs into pan. You should not hear a hiss, and the eggs should lie flat and still. If you hear sizzling or the whites flutter or bubble at all, turn down the heat. Cook 3 minutes or until the whites are mostly set, with some still-runny whites near the yolks. Tilt pan toward you so oil pools on the bottom edge; dip a spoon in the oil, and gently baste the uncooked patches of white until they are set. Be careful not to baste the yolks, or they\'ll cloud over like cataracts. Sprinkle with pepper and salt. Remove eggs from pan, leaving excess oil behind.</string>
    <string name="select">Select</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
</resources>